Guide to the Le Bayou Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Submissions, 1937-1963
  - General, 1937-1963
    - Roesgen-Champion, Marguerite; Paris, France, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Rojo Léon, Armando; Casablanca, Maroc, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Rondeau, Gaëtan; Nantes, France, 1948-1950 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Rosmant, Maurice; Sainte-Cécile, Belgique, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Rougerie, René; France, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Rousselot, Jean; Etang la Ville, France, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Rovida, Gino; Italie, 1953-1962 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Rubin, Jean; New York, 1954-1956 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Rudel, Yves Marie; France, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Sabarthez, Henri A.; France, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Saintonge, Jacques-André; Belgique, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Saisselin, Rémy G.; Ohio, 1957-1963 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Salinas, José, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Sandras, Michel; Le Puy, France, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Sauvabelin, Marie; France, 1955-1959 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Scalamandré, Raffaële, Italie, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Schaltin, Raymond; Paris, France, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Schaettel, Marcel; Bourges, France, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Schaffer, Aaron; Texas, 1942-1952 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Schepel, Dieuw; Netherlands, 1958-1962 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Schoell-Langlois, Marguerite; Paris, France, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Schwab, Raymond, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Sébastian, Pierre; Chicago, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Sechet, Françoise; Houston, Texas, undated (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Seeger, Alan, undated (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Seguin, Marc; Paris, France, 1949-1957 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Sellin, Eric; Pennsylvania, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Shamblir, Bill, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Shapiro, Norman Richard; Connecticut, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Shepherd, James C; Texas, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Sherwin, Judith J., 1956 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Sikirdji, Claudie; Grenoble, France, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Silberstein, Maurice; Liège, Belgique, 1945-1950 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Smal, Anne-Marie; Namur, Belgique, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Savoie, Soeur Marie Alberta; Kansas, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Solovieff, Georges; New York, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Sotiracopoulou, Agnès; Athènes, Grèce, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Soudeny, Jamal; Tunisie, 1948-1953 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Souffrin, Eileen; London, England, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Souffron, Paul; France, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Souvenance, Jean; Saint-Brieuc, France, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Spencer, James B., undated (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Spire, André; New York; Paris, France, 1942-1958 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Stack, Edward M.; Texas, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Stanley, Oma; Texas, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Stengers, Anne-Marie; Belgique, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Stenne, Robert-Ghislain; Verviers, Belgique, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Streiff, René; Rouen, France, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Sutcliffe, Frank Edmund; Manchester, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Tamin, Marion; Michigan, 1941-1943 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Tamin, Marion; Michigan, 1944-1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Tardy, G.; Algiers, Algérie, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Temple, F.J.; Montpellier, France, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Thaly, David; Fort de France, Martinique, 1941-1946 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Thériot, Marie del Norte; Louisiana, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Thettement, André, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Thierry, André; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1948, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Toetenel, Albert; Belgique, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Tordth, Shimsone; Maroc, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Tricou, Charles; Aniane, France, 1949-1963 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Tristan, Raymond; St. Mandé, France, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Troilliet, Gilbert; Genève, Suisse, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Turenne-des-Prés, F.; New York, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Underwood, Edna Worthley, 1938-1953 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Wintzen, Rene, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Submissions for Le Bayou, 1957-1963
    This subseries consists of 46 folders that contain rough draft materials for issues numbering 69 though 71, and for issues numbering 93 and 94. It is organized by issue number, by date, and then alphabetically.
    - No. 69; Printempts, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - No. 69; Printempts; La Derniere Passion Humaine de Verlaine; Seguin, Marc, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - No. 69; Printempts; Exégese des Chimeres; Lebois, André, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - No. 69; Printempts; Futee, la Genette…”; Pechyrand, Roger, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - No. 69; Printempts; Monologue de la Fourchette; Menanteau, Pierre, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - No. 69; Printempts; Neiges; Lavaud, Guy, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - No. 69; Printempts; Le Plus Curieux des Métiers; Lavaud, Guy, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - No. 69; Printempts; Visiteurs de la Fievre; Decreus, Juliette, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - No. 70; Été; Autour d’une Brochette de Savants; Bonmariage, Sylvain, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - No. 70; Été; fragment, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - No. 70; Été; Le Jugement de T.S. Eliot sur le “Baudelaire” de Swinburne Est-il Valable?; Marshall, Robert, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - No. 70; Été; A Propos de Marcel Proust; Bonmariage, Sylvain, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - No. 71; Automne; Mr. Briggs Chez l’Habitant; Chessex, Jean-Charles, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - No. 71; Automne; La Corneille; Loisy, Jean, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - No. 71; Automne; Geo Libbrecht, Poete Cosmique de l’Infini; Delmelle, Joseph, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - No. 71; Automne; Le Gris de Paris; Loisy, Jean, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - No. 71; Automne; Henri de Regnier…extrait d’une conference en vers; Gargour, Edouard; (Lauréat de l’Academie Française 1937-46 et 1953), 1957 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - No. 71; Automne; Heureux les Simples d’Espirit; Lebrau, Jean, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - No. 71; Automne; Itineraire de Jean de Boschere; Lebois, André, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - No. 71; Automne; Premier Apprentissage; Vaissiere, M.L., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - No. 71; Automne; La Symphonie Inachevée; Fédou, Armand, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - No. 71; Automne; Le Testament Spirituel de Jean de Boschere; Burucoa, Christiane, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - No. 71; Automne; Le Triomphe de la bêtise n’empêche pas qu’il y ait des poètes; Lavaud, Guy, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - No. 71; Automne; Trois Lettres inédites de Jean de Boschére à André Lebois, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Archives; Marti, Delphine, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Aux Approaches d’Emmanuel Looten à travers l’oeuvre et les commentaires; Poilvet le Guenn, Jean, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Aspects du Baroque Claudélien; Pearson, Yvonne Alfandari, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Ce Soir; de Sainte-Guidon, Robert, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Chagrin; Niezabytowska, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Chant de Danse Funébres; Katz; Joseph, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Charnier; Delmelle, Joseph, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Chasse a l’Homme; de Sainte-Guidon, Robert (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Le Clavier Sans Echo; Elot, Maryse, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; A Deux Eaux; Laffon, Rafael, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Forêt; Niezabytowska, Solange, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Gisant; Delmelle, Joseph, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Henri Perruchot a Choisi la Biographie; Périale, Marise, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Nos. 93-94. Printempts-Été; Instinct/Raison; Dion-Levesque, R., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Nos. 93-94. Printempts-Été; Je Suis Chez Moi; untitled; Histoire; Greene, Tatiana, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; L’Heure; Un Conte Ole, Raymond-Jean Lenoble (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Message; Heruieley, Henriette, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Notre Baudelaire; Humphrey, George, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Panache Blance; Ganne, Gilbert, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Pays des Bayous; Un Jour; Paysage Fait En Collage; Ventadour, Fanny, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Salve d’Avenir; Mathieu, André, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Nos. 93-94; Printempts-Été; Vestale des Lettres; Periale, Marise, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Subscriptions, 1934-1963
  This series consists of three boxes of documents relating to subscriptions, as well as an index card file. It includes general subscriptions, gift subscriptions, individual subscriptions, organizations, and universities. It also includes the materials that contain information concerning the exchange of Le Bayou with other publications, and the orders made by subscription companies. It is organized alphabetically, and then by date. The index card file is at the end.
  - General Subscriptions, 1938-1962
    This subseries consists of 6 folders that relate to subscriptions for Le Bayou from 1938 to 1962. There is also material relating to orders for Ballades de Mon Bayou. It is arranged alphabetically, and then by date.
    - Ballades de Mon Bayou; Ventes, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - 1938-1949 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - 1955-1957; 1959-1962 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Ventes au Numéro, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Gift Subscriptions, 1950-1955
    This subseries consists of one folder that contains gift subscription orders for Le Bayou from 1950 to 1955.
    - Gift Subscriptions, 1950-1955 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Individual Subscribers, 1941-1963
    This subseries consists of 172 folders that contain subscription information for individual subscribers, for Le Bayou from 1941 to 1963. It is organized alphabetically, and then by date.
    - Allard, Wilfred P.; United States Embassy, Paris; gift subscription, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Andrews, Bill; Oklahoma, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Archer, W.H.; Tennessee, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Asselineau, Roger; France, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Bachner, Dorothy; Illinois, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Bernard, Joseph; Illinois, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Bergerson, Jean; Montrèal, Canada, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Betza, Moria; New Jersey, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Blanch, Emma; Connecticut, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Bleibtreu, Kurt; Autriche, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Bouivhuis, Carol; New York, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Boussac, Guy; Paris, France, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Brown, Mary Jane; Ohio, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Capelle, Pierre J.; Champeix, France, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Carter, Betty; Texas, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Castel, J.H., 1944, 1950-1963 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Charrin, P; Houston, Texas, 1942-1962 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Dahlgren, Mildred; Illinois, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - De Buzelet, Jean; Paris, France, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Del Boca; B.; Italie, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - De Shazo, Marrion Z.; Texas, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Dreux, Audré, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Earl, Helen C.; Houston, Texas, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Elfers, F.L.E., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Engerrand, George C.; Texas, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Erzgovitch, Casamir; Pennsylvania, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Escale, Caroline; New York, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Fallet, Madame; Saint Quentin, France, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Farrell, Thomas A.; Massachusetts, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Fay, Eliot G.; Georgia, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Fédou, Armand Jean; Moux, France, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Foerster, Frere James; Ohio, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Fojtik, Sonja; Texas, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Forbes, Barbara; Regina, Canada, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Fouré-Selter, H.; Paris, France, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - French Consulate General; San Francisco, California, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Fuoc, Marguerite; New York, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Galli, Philippe; Italie, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Garcia, Angel; Cuba, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Garrison, W.E.; Houston, Texas, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Gastaldi; Santiago; Uruguay, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Glynn, Keith; New York, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Godes, Roger; Canada (bookshop), 1963 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Goldschmidt, Luaen; New York (bookshop), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Gulf, Harry; Colorado, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Graham, Neil H.; Alabama, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Graulich, John R.; Tennessee, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Guédry, Eugène; Louisiana, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Guyod, Hubert; Houston, Texas, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Haber, Pierre-Claude; New York, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Hamelin, André; Montréal, Canada, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Harrison, Mrs. Edwards; Houston, Texas, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Hauseux, Jacques; Liège, Belgique, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Hautefeuille, Jeande; Paris, France, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Havez, Jean; France, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Hayne, W.H.; Houston, Texas, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Heidsieck, E. John; New York, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Hendriksen, John H.; Utah, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Hennessy, J.; New Jersey, 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Henquet, Roger; Paris, France, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Herisson, C.D.; Grahamstown, South Africa, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Heyne, Otto; New York, 1960-1963 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Hill, Bessie; Colorado, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Hoffmann-Bretel, Julian; Autriche, 1950, 1958, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Honig, Maud J.; New Jersey, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Hoydts, Robert; Indiana, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Huot, Pierre; Nancy, France, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Iwané, Norio; Hilcari, Japan, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Jack, Alta; Texas, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Johnson, Robert B.; Massachusetts, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Jones, Richard O.; Houston, Texas, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Joot, Jacques; Michigan, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Josepha, Sister Margaret; Massachusetts, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Julian, Elmer; Illinois, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Kamm, Mother Pauline; Massachusetts, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Lacourcière, Luc; Québec, Canada, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Lajos, Pergovacz; Budapest, Hongrie, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Landry, Theodore E.; Louisiana, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Langlois, Paul-Etienne; Canada, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Lanoë, Julian; Nantes, France, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - LaPerriere, Denyse; Montrèal, Canada, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Lassalle, Félix; California, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Lavergne, Louis; Montréal, Canada, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Lebrat, Georges; France, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Lecler, S.; Olse, France, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Le Gariel, Jacques; Paris, France, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Léger, Louis; Louisiana, undated (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Lemaître, Henri; Vanves, France, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Le Mieux, Archibald R.; Massachusetts, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Lemieux, Armand; Illinois, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Lepaul, Jacqueline; France, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Libbrecht, Geo; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Lilly, Leo; New York, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Lindsay, Marshall; California, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Linkhorn, Renee; Ohio, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Long, Roy; Louisiana, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Lugton, Robert C.; Michigan, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Madore, Valens; Maine, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Maillet, Madame; Saint Quentin, France, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Mamet, C.; Ile Maurice, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Maness, V.L.; Texas, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Mantha, Hector; Montréal, Canada, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Marchesini, Cesare G.; Italie, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Marcus, Leslie; Arizona, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Marrache, Clauden; Syrie, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Marshall, James F.; California, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Martin, Jose; Texas, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Massis, Armand; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Masson, Mary, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Maystorovich, Frank; Kentucky, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - McCorkle, William; Delaware, undated (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Meshaka, Madame; St. Quentin, France, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Mimart, Mrs. Paul; Massachusetts, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Moeller, Ernest F.; New York, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Moiroux, Nicole; France, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Moreau, M.; Paris, France, undated (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Morize, Monsieur; Paris, France, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Morley, S.G.; California, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Morris, Lillian; Massachusetts, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Moss, J.M.; Houston, Texas, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Moulaert, Dr.; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Mulhenheim, Fréderic; Tennessee, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Nady, Mrs. Paul; California, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Namely, Mrs. John W.; Kentucky, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Nibbi, Gino; Italie, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Nodean, Gabriel; Massachusetts, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Outters, Marie; New York, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - P. & H. Bliss; Connecticut, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Perry, Sara A.; Colorado, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Pick, Martha; Indiana, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Poen, Kwik Wie; Indonésie, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Polioesky, R.; New York, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Ponin, Patti; New Jersey, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Price, Margaret Evans; New York, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Quolin, Roger; Belgique, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Radin, Adrienne B.; New York, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Ragner, Jacqueline; Iowa, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Raymond, Agnes G.; Rhode Island, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Rogers, M., undated (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Sionmelz, Toumelin Geneviéve; Maroc, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - Sackely, Ralph; Illinois, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Sandre, Paul; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Sawin, Dr. H.; Houston, Texas, 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Schaub-Koch, Emile; Genève, Suisse, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Schwarz, L.; Christchurch, New Zealand, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - Schwecke, Madeleine; Texas, undated (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - Serrault, Maurice; Tours, France, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - Seyrat, René; Paris, France, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - Shea, Carroll; Colorado, 1942-1944 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - Shelton, Fred V.; Houston, Texas, 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - Serebrakian, Lily; New York, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 151)
    - Silber, S.J.; Illinois, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 152)
    - Sister Georgiana, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 153)
    - Sitzler, Léon; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - Sorell, G.; New York, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - Souday, Guy; Harfleur, France, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 156)
    - Stevens, George; Ohio, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 157)
    - Stevenson, Mme. Ladelle; Houston, Texas, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - Strader, Albert M.; Michigan, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 159)
    - Strother, Mrs. Nelson; Maryland, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 160)
    - Tabbia, Angel Alberto; Argentina, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Thivierge, Helen; Maine, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 162)
    - Thomas, H.L.; Texas, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - Tison, John P.; Tennessee, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - Todd, G.; Michigan, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 165)
    - Tortra, Alain; France, undated (Box 8, Folder 166)
    - Toutonglie, Philippe; Washington, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 167)
    - Troseth, Mrs. Ralph; Houston, Texas, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 168)
    - Urban, Germainé; New York, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 169)
    - Urschla, Grete; Austriche, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 170)
    - Young, Neal E.; Houston, Texas, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 171)
    - Zorn, Jean; Arlon, Luxembourg, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 172)
  - Bookstores, Libraries, Organizations, and Universities, 1937-1963
    This subseries consists of roughly 1 and a half boxes of materials relating to subscriptions for Le Bayou by bookstores, libraries, universities, and other kinds of organizations. It is arranged alphabetically, and then by date.
    - Abilene Christian College; gift subscription, 1947-1948, 1951-1953, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 173)
    - Académie Ste. Anne; Massachusetts, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 174)
    - Agnes Scott College Library; Georgia, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 175)
    - Akademische Buchhandlung; Allegmagne, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 176)
    - Alabama Polytechnic Institute Library, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 177)
    - All Saints Episcopal College, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 178)
    - Alliance College Library; Pennsylvania, 1958-1960 (Box 8, Folder 179)
    - American Consulate; Martinique (Box 8, Folder 180)
    - American Library in Paris; gift subscription, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 181)
    - American University at Cairo; Egypte; gift subscription, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 182)
    - Amerika Institut Universitat-Munchen; Allegmagne; gift subscription, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 183)
    - Arkansas A&M; Arkansas; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 184)
    - Arkansas Polytechnic College; Arkansas, 1950-1952 (Box 8, Folder 185)
    - Arundel High School; Maryland, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 186)
    - Austin College Library; Texas, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 187)
    - Baldwin Wallace College; Ohio; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 188)
    - Baylor University Library; Texas, 1949-1962 (Box 8, Folder 189)
    - Beaufort High School; South Carolina, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 190)
    - Bibliothèque Franco-Americaine; Guadeloupe, 1958-1961 (Box 8, Folder 191)
    - Bibliotheca del Institut Frances de la Laguna; Mexique; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 192)
    - Bibliothèque de la Législature; Québec, Canada, 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 193)
    - Bibliothèque Lycee F. Eboue; Cayenne, French Guiana, 1959-1963 (Box 8, Folder 194)
    - Bibliothèque Nationale; Paris, France, 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 195)
    - Bibliothèque Royale de Belgique, 1948, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 196)
    - Birmingham Southern College; Alabama, 1950-1953 (Box 8, Folder 197)
    - Boston Public Library, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 198)
    - Boston University; Massachusetts; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 199)
    - Bradford Junior College; Massachusetts, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 200)
    - Brown Book Shop; Houston, Texas, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 201)
    - Care, Inc.; New York, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 202)
    - Centenary College of Louisiana, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 203)
    - Centre Culturel Americain, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 204)
    - Center High School Library; Texas, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 205)
    - Le Circle Artistique Français, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 206)
    - Clark College Library; Washington, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 207)
    - Colby Junior College, Fernald Library, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 208)
    - Columbia University Libraries; New York, 1945-1946, 1948-1962 (Box 8, Folder 209)
    - Cornell University; New York, 1954-1955, 1958-1959, 1960-1963 (Box 8, Folder 210)